(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T22:31:45.764669",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
待たれよ
Wait up!
ニコニコ
Smiles~
あらあら
Ara ara~
眠たい
I'm sleepy...
ちょこも眠たい
Choco is sleepy too...
いちごチョコ
Strawberry Choco!
待て待て待て
Wait, wait, wait!
どっち？
Which way?
やだやだやだやだ！
No, no, no, no!
どうもー！ホロライブ2期生悪魔の保健医、癒月ちょこでーす！
Hello! Hololive 2nd Gen demon school nurse, Yuzuki Choco here!
お前何人分じゃー！
How many people's worth are you?!
スパチャ Thank you! Thank you very much!
Super Chat, thank you! Thank you very much!
ほら、豚、登って！頑張って、豚！
Come on, pig, climb! Do your best, pig!
ほら、豚！こっちよ、こっち！どっち？
Come on, pig! Over here, over here! Which way?
はいはいはいはい！
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
何だろう？
What is it?
何年やってると思ってるんですかー！
How many years do you think I've been doing this?!
先生に向かって何ですか、その言葉遣いは！友達じゃないんですよ！いいですか？
What's with that language toward your teacher?! We're not friends! Got it?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
Because I'm Yuzuki Choco-sensei!
お、やばい！うわー！
Oh no! Woah!
美味しかったのー
That was delicious~
あ、違う！ダメ！あー！
Ah, no! Stop! Ah!
ちょこしかおらん
There's only Choco!
豚動いた！豚あいつ！
The pig moved! That pig!
はい、いらっしゃいませー
Yes, welcome~
どこ行きよるん？行き過ぎ！
Where are you going? You went too far!
おやすみー
Good night~
はぁ〜 いい天気の保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい
Haa~ On such a nice day, I want to take a nap on the infirmary bed.
ずる休み 許されない 保健室は神聖なの
Playing hooky isn't allowed! The infirmary is sacred!
サボってる？ ちょっとだけ 誰も来なきゃやる気出ない
Slacking off? Just a bit! If no one comes, I have no motivation.
ちょこちょこ センセーション ちょこちょこ センセーション
Choco-Choco Sensation! Choco-Choco Sensation!
このままじゃ私 ダメみたい
At this rate, I'm going to turn useless...
大きなフトン抱え 2回目の「おやすみなさい」
Hugging a big futon, saying "Good night" for the second time.
ごめんなさい 風邪だけで寝させて 先生モード シャットダウン
Sorry, just let me sleep off this cold. Sensei mode shutdown!
夢見る ふわふわ ずっとこうして眠りたい
Dreaming fluffy dreams, I want to sleep like this forever.
ありがとう ぽかぽか ちょっと休憩してるだけ
Thank you, so warm and cozy. I'm just taking a short break.
油断大敵ね
Carelessness is the greatest enemy!
急に君が来るなんて ねぇどこかが悪いの？
You coming by so suddenly... Hey, is something wrong?
何かを期待しているのかな
Are you expecting something, I wonder?
揺れる心 巡る感情 ドキドキ甘いセンセーション
Swaying heart, swirling feelings, a heart-throbbing sweet sensation!
癒されたい 甘えていたい 頼られたい ちょこセンセーション
Wanting to be healed, spoiled, relied on! Choco Sensation!
君の視線 君の体温 分かっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your warmth... Even if I feel them, love can't be measured.
元気なのにため息出ちゃうの
Even though you're fine, you end up sighing.
少しね
Just a little...
なにかの病
Some kind of illness.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて 毎急行便
But I can't move until my heart throbs, so deliver excitement via special express!
ずる休み また来たの？ 保健室は神聖なの
Playing hooky? Did you come again? The infirmary is sacred!
サボってた？ ちょっとだけ やっぱり君に居てほしい
Slacking off? Just a bit! After all, I want you to be here.
明日は 週末 お休み なんだよ
Tomorrow is the weekend! It's a day off!
家飲み 最高！
Drinking at home is the best!
引き籠り 最高！
Being a shut-in is the best!
もちろん ノーメイク
Of course, no makeup!
チャイムが鳴ったら 白衣着ます！
When the chime rings, I'll put on my lab coat!
さぁすべてを見せて 聴診器当て出来ないじゃん
Come on, show me everything! I can't use the stethoscope like this!
何を隠してるの 鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
What are you hiding? I can hear how fast your heart is beating!
見せて手心 巡るシャツを 正常保ってる緊張感
Show me some leniency, through your shirt, keeping tension at normal levels.
愛されたい 頼られたい 高まりたい ちょこセンセーション
Wanting to be loved, relied on, hyped up! Choco Sensation!
君の重み 君の匂い 分かっても愛は測れない
Your weight, your scent... Even if I know them, love can't be measured.
大好きだから
Because I love you so much...
ため息ついちゃうよ
I end up sighing.
やっぱり
As expected,
それは恋の病
that's love sickness.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて 毎急行便
But I can't move until my heart throbs, so deliver excitement via special express!
魔界だって
Whether in the demon realm
この世界だって
or in this world,
みんな癒やしが
everyone needs
必要だから
healing after all!
ちょこちょこ センセーション ちょこちょこ センセーション ちょこちょこ センセーション
Choco-Choco Sensation! Choco-Choco Sensation! Choco-Choco Sensation!
絶対君も虜にしたい！
I definitely want to make you fall for me too!
ゆらゆら 心巡る感情
Swaying emotions swirling in my heart
ちょこせんせーしょん
Choco Sensation!
癒されたい？ 甘えていたい？
Do you want to be healed? Want to be spoiled?
大胆？ ちょこせんせーしょん
Boldly? Choco Sensation!
君の視線 君の体温
Your gaze, your body temperature,
わかっても 恋は測れない
even if I understand them, love can't be measured.
元気なのに ため息しちゃう
Even though I'm doing fine, I end up sighing.
もしかしてもー手遅れ？
Could it already be too late?
でも どっちどっちするまで 動けないから
But I can't move until I make up my mind,
ドキドキ 運んできて マイチューン
so bring me butterflies, my tune!
ちょこちょこ せんせーしょん (イェイ)
Choco Choco Sensation! (Yay!)
吐息も ダメにしたい
I want to melt away even your sighs...
はい！ということで！
All right! So with that...
癒月ちょこ生誕祭 2026 始まりましたー！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Festival 2026 has begun!
見て見てー！
Look, look!
一曲目から、ちょこ...
From the very first song, Choco...
生まれ変わりましたー！
...has been reborn!
いやー、今日はね
Yeah, today...
原点回帰ということで
...returning to my roots,
ちょこの、なんと保健室ステージなのー！
...this is Choco's nurse's office stage!
いや、ちょっと保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって
Even the nurse's office got a bit of a makeover,
めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりましたー！
and turned out super cute!
学園ドラマとかできそうだよねー？
Looks like we could film a school drama here, right?
今日は生まれ変わった ニューちょこと
Today, with this reborn New Choco
素敵なゲスト様をいっぱい呼んでライブをしていくんだけど
and lots of wonderful guests, we'll be putting on a live show, but...
その前に！
...before that!
みんなちょこのこと、もっと見たいよねー？
Everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも！まだダメだよー。
Ah, but! Not just yet.
これから来る、お二人に...
To the two guests coming up...
ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいましたー！
...I asked them to hold a photoshoot for Choco!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう！
So let me introduce them right away!
ノエル様ー！
Noel-sama!
ラミィ様ー！
Lamy-sama!
きたよー！
We're here!
ちょこ先生！
Choco-sensei!
せーの、ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとうー！
One, two... Choco-sensei, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！嬉しいー！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
ということでね、今回はね、この可愛い両手に花で、可愛いお二人に...
So then, this time, blessed with these two cuties by my side...
ちょっとね、ちょこの撮影会をしていってもらうと思うんですけど
...I'm going to have you two do a photoshoot of Choco, but...
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします！
...first, please introduce yourselves!
ノイちゃんから！
Starting with Noi-chan!
はい！コンマッスル！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル...
Yes! Kon-muscle! I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Gen...
と！
...and!
はい！ホロライブ5期生のかおがかんぞう雪花ラミィです！
Yes! From Hololive 5th Gen, "My face is a liver," Yukihana Lamy!
今日はよろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well today!
まあね、ちょっとちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところを
Well, showing off how cute Choco-sensei has gotten,
ちょっと団長、頑張って攻めていこうと思いますので
Danchou here will do her best to go all out,
よろしくお願いします！
so please look forward to it!
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy wants to push it to the limit, too!
いや撮影会やるならちょっとね、このお二人を呼ぶしかないかなーって思って、呼んじゃいました！
Well, if I was going to do a photoshoot, I just had to invite you two!
しかもしかも、ちょっと後でこの3人から... なんとお知らせもあるみたいなので！
And what's more, the three of us have an announcement later!
えっ！気になる気になる！
What?! I'm so curious!
撮影会の後で、皆様楽しみに待っててください！
After the photoshoot, everyone please look forward to it!
それじゃあちょっとこちらで撮影会、よろしくお願いします！
Well then, please go ahead with the photoshoot over here!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
えほ えほ えほ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
お！なんかすごいところ来たぞ！
Oh! We came somewhere amazing!
えー！すごい！かわいい！
Woah! Amazing! So cute!
可愛いでしょうー！可愛いでしょうー！
Isn't it cute?! Isn't it cute?!
撮影会はちょこのここの診察室でやりまーす！
We'll do the photoshoot right here in Choco's examination room!
やー！ちょこ先生の診察室ー！
Yay! Choco-sensei's examination room!
すげー可愛い！
Super cute!
いいでしょ、いいでしょー！
Isn't it great? Isn't it great?
でもさ、診察室だけど ベッドは？ ベッドどこ？
But wait, it's an examination room, where's the bed?
なんかパネルもあれー？ あれ使う？
Also, what about that panel over there? Are we using it?
あ、そー、とんでもないのがあるけど... これダメなの？
Ah, well, there is something crazy, but... is this no good?
そこはあとのメン限で使うの！
That's for later in the members-only stream!
えー！ メン限！？ そうなんだ！
What?! Members-only?! I see!
ちょっとね、ベッドとか、撮影会とかシチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって...
I'm thinking of doing a photoshoot and situational drama on the bed later...
シチュエーションドラマ！？ とんでもないことしようとしてるー！
A situational drama?! She's trying to do something crazy!
いや、そうなんですよー。
Yeah, that's right.
まぁね、ま、それは置いといて。
Well, putting that aside for now.
ちょっと今回は、ふたりに撮影をしてもらいたいので、まずは...
This time, I'd like you two to take photos of me, so first...
ラミィ様には...
For Lamy-sama...
カメラ！本格的な...！ すごい！ カメラ来たー！
A camera! A real professional one...! Wow! Here comes the camera!
そしてノエル様にはこちらー！ じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, here's this! Ta-da!
チョコのBANを守るために特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
It's a mosaic stick specially made to protect Choco from getting BANned!
特別？！ すげー！ モザイク来た！
Special?! Awesome! A mosaic feature!
ボタンで、このモザイクの荒さを変えれるらしい！
Apparently, you can change the blurriness of the mosaic with this button!
今めっちゃ荒くなってる... あ、本当だ！ 薄くできる！
It's super blurry right now... Oh, it's true! You can lighten it!
あ、本当だ！ すげー！
Oh, it's true! Amazing!
でもなんか荒い方が、むしろ良いまであるな、これ。
But honestly, having it more pixelated might actually be better.
確かに！ 隠せてるやん！ これ配信守りますよ！
Indeed! It hides it! We'll protect the stream!
じゃあこの配信を守ってください！
Then please protect this stream!
それでは撮影会、スタート！
Then, let the photoshoot session start!
まずはやっぱ全身！
First, definitely a full-body shot!
いつものチョコせんのこんな感じ？
The usual Choco-sen pose like this?
美しい！ あぁ〜！ 良いね良いね！
Beautiful! Ah~! Nice, nice!
いや、可愛い！ もうここちょっとまずいんじゃないの？
No way, so cute! Wait, isn't this part a bit risky right here?
まずいかな？
Is it risky?
逆にノリノリなんですけど！
On the contrary, she's super into it!
ちょっとここ揺れて... モザイクが追いついてない！
It's shaking a bit here... The mosaic can't keep up!
じゃあノエル様頑張って！
Then Noel-sama, keep working hard!
こうやってね、あ、いい感じで、うんうん。
Like this, ah, nice feeling, yeah, yeah.
ちょっとジャンプしてもらって見てもらっても...
How about jumping a little bit to see?
あ、やばいやばいやばい！ めっちゃやばい！ ダメダメダメ！
Ah, dangerous, dangerous! So risky! No no no!
あいあいあい！ あら〜！
Ai ai ai! Oh my~!
ちょっとせっかくだから椅子とかも座っちゃう？
Since we're here, why don't you sit on a chair?
うん、椅子ね、ここにありますね。
Yeah, there's a chair right here.
あー、良いね！ めっちゃ可愛い！
Ah, nice! So cute!
あ、そう！ チョコね、底が赤なの！
Ah, yes! Choco's shoe soles are red!
ちょっ... ま、まずい...！ ありがとうございます！
W-Wait, that's risky...! Thank you very much!
底がね、赤なの！ これー！
The soles are red, see? This!
大丈夫？ あ、でもなんか見えてないからね。
Is it okay? Ah, but nothing is showing.
大丈夫でした、セーフですね。 守ってます！
It was okay, safe! We're protecting it!
いいね、じゃあこう、どんどん上を見てもらって...
Nice, then keep looking... up at the camera...
あ、良いねー！ あら可愛いー！
Ah, nice~! Oh, so cute~!
見えてるー？ 見えてるよ、見えてるー！
Can you see? We can see, we can see!
あら、可愛いー！ いいねー！
Oh, so cute~! Nice~!
え、ちなみにラミィさん...
By the way, Lamy-san...
椅子に座って先生ポーズも希望してたけど...
You also requested a teacher pose sitting in the chair...
先生ポーズって何だ？ こんな感じ？
What's a teacher pose? Like this?
あー！ いい！ 非常によい！ モザイクいらないね、これ！
Ah! Good! Very good! We don't need a mosaic for this!
チョコせんの魅力が溢れすぎてて...
Choco-sen's charm is overflowing so much...
良いですねー！ 素晴らしい！
Nice~! Wonderful!
え、じゃあ団長も良いですか？ お尻フリフリを...
Eh, then can the Captain request one too? A butt shake...
フリフリ、えっと後ろ向いてもらって...
Shake, shake, um, please turn around...
白衣越しだけど、フリフリ！ あ、良いねー！
Through the lab coat, shake shake! Ah, nice~!
白衣ってこれ脱いでほしいんだけど、脱げないの？
I want her to take off this lab coat, can't it be removed?
脱げるけど、メン限でって言ってたー！
It can be removed, but I said that's for members-only!
団長、ガニ股好きで...
The Captain likes crab stance...
団長ガニ股好きなん... うわー！
Captain likes crab stance... Woah!
ガニ股ー！ ガニ股助かるー！
Crab stance~! Crab stance is a godsend~!
ガニ股ー！ これちょっとモザイク！ モザイク！
Crab stance~! Wait, mosaic! Mosaic!
ちょっと見えてるもん！ モザイクお願いします！
It's showing! Mosaic, please!
モザイクが... 逆にやばい！
The mosaic is... worse, on the contrary!
やばいやばいやばい！
Risky, risky, risky!
ふぅー！ どんどん行こう、どんどん行こう！
Whew~! Let's keep going, let's keep going!
ラストはアイドルだから、とびきり可愛いアイドルおねがいします！
For the last shot, since you're an idol, please give us a super cute idol pose!
はい！ えー、可愛いー！
Here! Wow, so cute~!
あ、いいね。ヘルシー！
Ah, nice. Healthy!
可愛い！
So cute!
顔のアップいいね
Close-up of the face is great!
たまらんです！可愛い！
Irresistible! So cute!
オッケー！いっぱいいただいた！
Okay! Got plenty of photos!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので！
We'll continue this in the members-only stream!
メン限では歌も撮影会も、シチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やってみます！
In members-only, we'll have a song, a photo shoot, and two situation dramas!
楽しみ！
Looking forward to it!
ちなみにタイトルとかあるの？そのシチュエーションドラマって
By the way, are there titles for those situation dramas?
今回のタイトルが、先生とベッドで...
The title this time is "With Teacher in Bed...
...特別バレンタイン！
...Special Valentine!"
あと、診察室で甘い処方箋をっていう...
And also "Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room"...
甘ーい！最高すぎる！
So sweet! That's the best!
目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて...
For the perspective, we had the cameraman lie down on the bed...
みんなが本当に見えるように、撮影機が覆いかぶさるようにいろんな画角で撮っていったと思います！
...so everyone can see it clearly from various angles!
楽しみ！お楽しみに！
Looking forward to it! Look forward to it!
ということでそろそろお時間が迫ってきたので...
And with that, time is running short...
ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います！
...so we'll head back to the live stage!
急げ！急げ！
Hurry! Hurry!
はーい！というわけで...
Alright! So...
この後それぞれデュエットしてもらうんだけど...
...after this, each pair will perform a duet...
最後に3人でも歌うので楽しみにしててください！
...and lastly, all three of us will sing, so please look forward to it!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
それではお着替えに行きましょうか！
Shall we go change now?
すごい！リボンもついてる！可愛い！
Amazing! It even has ribbons! So cute!
じゃあカーテンの裏でお着替えに行ってきます！
Well then, we're off to change behind the curtain!
それでは聞いてください
Now then, please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
どろどろ とろり べいびー
Melting, dripping, baby
とろけちゃって catch me だーりん
Melted away, catch me darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり きゅるきゅる
Pure, pure cocoa, softly, sparklingly
ワン ツー
One, two
なんか眠れない夜には
On nights when I can't fall asleep
お散歩 特別パーティータイム
A walk, a special party time
2人きり (やったー)
Just the two of us (Yay!)
あの角曲がれば ベンチしかない公園だよ
Turn that corner, and it's a park with only a bench
蒸し暑い空気の中 迷い込むんだ
Into the humid night air, we wander
コンビニちょっと寄り道 (買い出し)
Stopping by the convenience store (Shopping)
アイスじゃなくって、これがいい
Not ice cream, I want this
缶のお酒 ほろ酔い
Canned alcohol, feeling tipsy
ウインクでストロング！
With a wink, strong!
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラブで潰して (お願い)
Liqueur can't get me drunk anymore, crush me with love (Please)
お砂糖はマシマシで
Extra sugar, please
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ、溶かして？
Melt it in this scorching heat, okay?
ごくって飲んで
Gulp it down
クセのある私を大事にしてよね
Treasure me, quirks and all
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
どろどろ とろり べいびー
Melting, dripping, baby
とろけちゃって catch me だーりん
Melted away, catch me darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり きゅるきゅる
Pure, pure cocoa, softly, sparklingly
ワン ツー
One, two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely path home
ふらふら 特別ボーナスタイム
Unsteadily, a special bonus time
手を繋ごう (にゃんにゃん)
Let me hold your hand (Meow meow)
大きめTシャツ 君に借りた
Borrowed your oversized T-shirt
ありがとーって 匂わせみたいにして 困らせたいんだ
Saying thanks, wearing your scent to tease and trouble you
コンビニまた寄っちゃった (楽しい)
Stopped by the convenience store again (Fun)
もう1本だけのよわいやつ
Just one more weak drink
テンパリングが大事！
Tempering is important!
アツすぎても飽きちゃって
Even if it's too hot, I get bored of it.
冷たいのはダメ (やだもん)
Cold things are no good (No way)
チョコみたいな私を
Treat me like chocolate
プレシャスにして扱って
Treat me like I'm precious
微炭酸のお酒で
With lightly carbonated alcohol
しゅわしゅわしゅわ〜
Shu-wa-shu-wa-shu-wa~
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless you convey it
恋してる証拠に
As proof that I'm in love
ここでちゅーってして
Give me a kiss right here
夜空のグラスに キラキラ溢して
Spilling sparkles into the glass of the night sky
息もできないくらいにもうだって
To the point where I can't even breathe, anymore
だって…
Because...
恋に溺れて
Drowning in love
君の熱で溶けた そのまんまで食べてよ
If I melt in your heat, eat me just like that
手にベトベト付いちゃって
Sticky all over your hands
一生 一生
Together forever
缶のお酒 ほろ酔い
Canned alcohol, tipsy
ウインクでストロング！
Winking with Strong Zero!
リキュールじゃもう酔えない
Liqueur can't make me drunk anymore
ラブで潰して (お願い)
Crush me with love (Please)
お砂糖はマシマシで
With extra sugar
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ、溶かして？
Melt me with the scorching heat, won't you?
ゴクって飲んで
Drink it down in one gulp
癖のある私だからさ
Because I'm a quirky girl
君が選ばれた サマーチョコレート
You were chosen, Summer Chocolate
どろんどろん とろり ベイビー
Muddy, gooey, baby
とろけちゃって キャッチ ミー ダーリン
Melt and catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり
Pure, pure cocoa, fluffy
きゅるきゅる ワンツー！
Curu-curu, one, two!
What's up, Japan?
Can you hear me?
It's radio time!
No money, no job?
Too much bad news?
There's no reason to be down.
It's time to get up!
We have a hot new song
that's from AKB48
to make you feel good:
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie!
So dance, Japan, crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
[Title: Fortune Cookie in Love]
あなたのことが好きなのに
I like you so much,
私にまるで興味ない
but you're not interested in me at all.
何度目かの失恋の準備
I'm already preparing for my bajillionth heartbreak.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
周りを見れば大勢の
When I look around,
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
there are so many cute girls everywhere.
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You don't notice a plain flower like me.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れる Music
To the music playing in the cafeteria...
ぼんやり聴いていたら
as I listen absentmindedly...
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
before I know it, to the beat,
つま先から動き出す
my toes start moving.
止められない今の気持ち
I can't stop this feeling right now.
カモカモカモカモベイビー
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, baby!
占ってよ
Tell my fortune,
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
fortune cookie in love!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future's not so bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
Gotta show a smile to bring luck your way.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of my heart,
運勢 今日よりもよくしよう
gonna make my luck even better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life's not a lost cause, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
Shocking miracles do happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I've got a hunch we'll fall in love somewhere.
あなたにちゃんと告りたい
I want to properly confess to you,
だけど自分に自信ない
but I don't have confidence in myself.
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can already imagine your reaction,
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いい子がいいなんて 男の子は言うけれど
Guys say they like girls with good personalities,
ルックスがアドバンテージ
but good looks are an advantage.
いつだって可愛い子が 人気投票1位になる
Cute girls are always the ones who win 1st place in popularity contests.
プリーズ プリーズ プリーズ オーベイビー
Please, please, please, oh baby,
私 も見て
look at me too.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie in love!
その殻 さあ壊してみよう
Come on, let's break through that shell!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
先の展開 神様も知らない
Not even God knows how things will unfold.
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of tears!
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is overflowing with love,
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
making you forget all the sad things that happened.
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
Tomorrow, different winds will blow.
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, baby!
占ってよ
Tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie in love!
未来はそんなに悪くないよ
The future isn't all that bad!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
To bring good luck, show a smile!
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of the heart!
運勢 今日よりも良くしよう
Let's make our luck even better than today!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't a lost cause, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A shocking miracle will happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling we'll fall in love somewhere.
君が好きって言ったら君が好き
If I say I like you, I like you!
ぴゅあらぶ ぴゅあらぶ
Pure love, pure love!
あのね乙女は本気出すとすごいんです
You know, when a maiden gets serious, she's amazing!
ワンツー いずれ執筆 あの手この手で
One-two, writing a recipe, trying this and that,
ライバルを出し抜くの
to outsmart all my rivals!
全部計算済み レシピ通り
Everything's calculated according to the recipe!
好きなタイプを聞いてみたりして
Asking about your preferred type,
不意に逢ってみたりして
bumping into you unexpectedly,
上目遣いで甘えて
looking up with sweet eyes and acting cute,
すでに完璧！
it's already perfect!
あー！手が滑った！
Ah! My hand slipped!
つまみ食いしたらなくなっちゃった！
I snuck a sample bite and now it's all gone!
恨んでやるー！
I'll hold a grudge!
時にはファンキー 苦いのはNGで
Sometimes funky, bitter stuff is an NG!
女の子の季節だもん 全部思い通りになってよね
It's the girls' season, so make everything go as planned!
君は私と結ばれます！
You are destined to end up with me!
本命あげちゃう メルティ
Giving you my true love chocolate, Melty!
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
Won't hand you over to anyone in this great war!
オトしちゃいます メルティ
I'm going to win you over, Melty!
それじゃ手と手つないじゃおう 内緒のデート
So let me hold your hand on a secret date!
スウィーティ スウィーティ キス 甘くていいの
Sweety, sweety kiss, sweet is fine!
スウィーティ スウィーティ ハグ こういうのが一推しでしょ
Sweety, sweety hug, this is your top choice, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対譲らない覚悟です 本気なのです
It's my first love, so I'm prepared to never yield! I'm dead serious!
目を見て言って 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me your true feelings!
ぴゅあらぶ ぴゅあらぶ
Pure love, pure love!
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' Battlefield!
なんのこれしき喋ってんの？
What on earth are you talking about?
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' Battlefield!
意識妄想がショート！
My consciousness and delusions short-circuit!
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' Battlefield!
大丈夫 へこたれないもん！
I'm okay, I won't lose heart!
惚れさせた方が勝ちです！
Whoever makes the other fall in love wins!
隠し味全部食べちゃった！
I ate all the secret ingredients!
砂糖の量は愛の量！
The amount of sugar is the amount of love!
間違えた！これ塩だった！
I made a mistake! This was salt!
乱心！
Madness!
調理指導手伝ってはいる！
I am helping out with cooking guidance!
真心込めてラッピング！
Wrapping it with all my heart!
自分も本気モードでいく！
I'm going into serious mode too!
祈る ラブ＆ピース
Praying for Love & Peace!
何度も試作した 予行練習もした
I made prototype after prototype, and I even rehearsed it.
弱気になになどなるな
Don't lose your nerve!
大丈夫 自分史上一番かわいい私なんだから
It'll be fine, because I'm the cutest version of myself ever!
君は私と結ばれます
You and I will end up together,
結ばれる運命なのです
because we are fated to be together!
本命あげちゃう めるてぃー！
I'll give you my favorite, Melty!
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war where I won't give you up to anyone!
ときめいちゃいます？ めるしー♡
Does your heart flutter? Mercy♡
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃう？ 内緒のデート
So shall we hold hands? A secret date!
すぅぃーてぃー すぅぃーてぃー キス
Sweety, sweety kiss
甘くていいの
Sweet is just right!
すぅぃーてぃー すぅぃーてぃー ハグ
Sweety, sweety hug
こういうのがいいっしょ？
You like this kind of thing, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対譲らない覚悟です
It's my first love, so I'm prepared to never yield!
本気なのです
I'm completely serious!
目を見て言って？ 君の気持ち
Look me in the eye and tell me your feelings.
ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure, pure, pure, pure love!
ぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure, pure love!
はい！ということで、私たち3人の新曲でしたー！
Yes! So that was our new song from the three of us!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いい曲でしたー！
It was a great song!
改めまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にですね、コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど、
Once again, this new song "Hatsukoi Daisensou" is a collaboration track with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama.
今回作詞作曲をMEDAN様、書籍編曲を洋介様にお願い致しました！
For this song, MEDAN-sama handled the lyrics and composition, and Yosuke-sama did the arrangement!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いや、今回のテーマが、バレンタインの日に3人の可愛い女の子たちが1人の男の子を手に入れるために、バチバチに出し抜き合おうとするみたいな、
The theme this time is about three cute girls competing fiercely on Valentine's Day to win over one boy, trying to outsmart each other...
なるほど！
I see!
息巻いたテーマの楽曲となっております！
It's a song with a very spirited theme!
いいね！可愛い！可愛い！
That's great! So cute! So cute!
そう！いやもう3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので、
Right! All three of our voices together turned it into such an awesome idol song!
ぜひぜひ皆様聴いてください！
Everyone, please be sure to give it a listen!
何回も聴きたいな！
I want to listen to it over and over!
ね！何回も聴いていける曲なのかなー！
Right? It's a song you can listen to over and over again!
いや、こちらの楽曲は、この後24時から、2月15日0時からですね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
Well, this song will be available on various music streaming sites starting at midnight, February 15th at 00:00!
やったらー！聴ける！
Yay! We can listen to it!
配信されます！そしてね、この配信後すぐに、この楽曲のー、
It'll be out! And right after this live stream ends...
MVが公開されます！
...the music video will be released!
やったー！
Yay!
いや、ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聴いて、MVの方にもちょっと感想とかね、コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなーって思います！
We'd love it if everyone listened to it a lot and left comments and impressions on the MV as well!
お願いします！
Please do!
じゃあね、2人とも今日はありがとう！
Alright then, thank you both so much for today!
お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy birthday!
引き続きね、待っててください！
Please keep waiting for what's coming next!
ありがとう！それじゃあ、おさらばじゃ！おさらば！
Thank you! Well then, farewell! Farewell!
そして、ここからライブ後半となります！
And from here on, we're entering the second half of the live stream!
まだまだゲストパートとか、あと最後に重大告知もあるので！
We still have guest segments and a major announcement at the end!
皆様、一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
Everyone, let's have fun together!
それでは、次のゲストはこちら！
Now then, here is the next guest!
大人なフリして。
[Title: Pretending to Be Grown-Up.]
急に「会いたい」って
Suddenly saying "I want to see you,"
いつものように準備してる
I get ready like I always do.
午前0時過ぎの終電で向かうって
I replied that I'd head over on the last train past midnight,
返信返した
and sent the text back.
やめときなよって言われても
Even if people tell me to stop...
また 会いに行く
I'm going to see you again,
会いたいから
because I want to see you.
ドレスアップに落ち合う 街の中では少し冷たい
Dressed up, we meet in town, but you're a bit cold.
慣れないワイン 強がりのみほしてしまっては ふらふら
Acting tough, I down the unfamiliar wine and get dizzy.
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you start disliking me?
下手くそにしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess up?
少し残しておきたくない
I don't want to leave anything behind.
ちょっと期待してね
Expect a little from me,
ずっと見栄張ってね
always showing off, right?
周りばかり気にして生きてる
Living while caring only about what's around me.
ちょっと優越感
A slight sense of superiority,
でもなんか淋しくて
but somehow feeling lonely.
本当の自分じゃ生き苦しくて
It's suffocating living as my real self.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
pushing myself even though I'm not like that.
味のしないキスでも
Even with a tasteless kiss,
やっぱり一番嬉しくて
it still makes me the happiest.
取り繕った私は可愛いかな
Am I cute when I put on a front?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me so tight tonight that I might break.
今にも切れそうな糸で繋がってる恋だね
It's a love connected by a thread that seems ready to snap.
私が諦めたらきっと簡単に消えちゃうね
If I give up, it'll surely vanish so easily.
引き止めるにはどうする？
What should I do to hold you back?
生ぬるかったらどうする？
What if it's half-hearted?
不器用な自分をからめ合って
Entangling our awkward selves together.
通知チェックしてね
Checking notifications,
息苦しい部屋で
in a suffocating room.
他の子と比べてばかりいた
I kept comparing myself to other girls.
一番見てほしい
I want you to look at me the most,
目の前のあなたは
but you right in front of me...
どこか違う景色見てる
...are looking at a different scenery somewhere else.
いつも優しいフリして
Always pretending to be gentle,
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
smiling even though you're not like that.
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get,
心は遠く感じて
the further away your heart feels.
少しだけ背伸びして
Stretching myself just a little bit,
本当が分かるよ
I see the truth.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight so tight that I forget everything.
自分がもっと強ければ
If only I were stronger,
サヨナラを言えるのにな
I could say goodbye.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
pushing myself even though I'm not like that.
ふと見せる優しさが
The kindness you suddenly show,
ずっと忘れられなくて
I can never forget it.
取り繕った私は可愛いかな
Am I cute when I put on a front?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me so tight tonight that I might break.
突然あふれ出した涙
Tears suddenly spilling over,
私があほだよね
I'm so foolish, aren't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると
I thought you'd turn to look at me someday,
思っていたのもいいから
but that's fine too.
取り繕った私が流れていく
My feigned self washes away.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight so tight that I forget everything.
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always look sleepy,
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
you always look bored,
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
you always look like you're in trouble,
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
and you're always on your smartphone.
本当はテンション高いのに
Even though you're actually energetic,
あたしと居るとき超低いし
when you're with me, your energy is super low.
あんまり自分悪くなくない？
Don't you think I'm not really at fault?
嫌い大嫌いどうでもいい
I hate you, I despise you, whatever!
言ったら僕も言うけどさ
If you say that, I'll say it too, but...
ちっちゃいことですぐ怒るし
You get mad over little things so easily,
言い返したらすぐ泣くし
and if I talk back, you cry right away.
ごめんねと言っても許してくれないし
Even if I apologize, you won't forgive me.
その割に1時間経てば
Yet after just one hour goes by,
お腹減った早くおごれとか言うし
you say "I'm hungry, hurry up and buy me food."
あーなんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are!
ちくしょうもう知らないぞ
Darn it, I don't care anymore!
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love...
苦い苦い秘密のチョコレート
...is a bitter, bitter secret chocolate.
デコレーションをちりばめて
Let's adorn it with decorations,
彩って食べちゃおうか
color it, and eat it up!
苦い苦い愛のタマテバコ
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
a future-flavored, mysterious chocolate.
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If we warm it up and mix it, surely,
いつかお口に合う味になるの
someday it will become a flavor to your liking!
ねぇねぇちょっといいかな
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
なあに？
What is it?
さっきはあのね、ごめんね
Um, I'm sorry about earlier.
何が？
For what?
いつもモヤっとなるじゃん
You always end up feeling uncertain, right?
それで？
And?
今日はこれを渡したくて
So I wanted to give you this today.
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Words alone aren't enough, so...
だから？
So...?
受け取ってくれないかな
Won't you accept it?
何を？
Accept what?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being by my side!
わかったよそれ
Alright, I get it!
あなたの優しさについつい甘えちゃう
I end up taking advantage of your kindness,
誰よりも近いから素直になれない
because you're closer to me than anyone, I can't be honest.
君の一生懸命さについつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting because of how earnest you are,
誰よりも一番大好きなのに
even though I love you more than anyone else.
甘い甘い夢のタカラバコ
A sweet, sweet treasure chest of dreams,
奇跡味の最初のチョコレート
a miracle-flavored first chocolate.
二人だけのイノベーションを
An innovation meant for just the two of us,
探して組み立てたら賑わおうか
let me search for it, build it, and celebrate!
苦い苦い日々のケショウバコ
A cosmetic box of bitter, bitter days,
世界味の最初のチョコレート
a world-flavored first chocolate.
冷めきって割れないように
So that it doesn't cool down and break,
大事につつんで生涯の完成形
let me wrap it carefully into a lifelong masterpiece!
いつだって
Always,
やめる時も
even through bad times,
どんな日も
no matter what day,
そうずっと
yes, forever.
健やかなるときも
Even through good times,
誓って
I swear,
違う二人を分かつまで
until death do our different selves part...
愛してる
I love you.
僕もそうさ
Me too.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
そばにいる
I'll be by your side.
なんて嘘かもよ
That might be a lie, though.
ああそうかい 僕も適当に言った
Ah, is that so? I was just kidding around too!
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet...
苦い苦い
Bitter, bitter...
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
a secret, universe-flavored chocolate.
二人だけのデコレーションを
A decoration meant for just the two of us,
ちりばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
let me adorn it, color it, and eat it up!
苦い苦い愛のタマテバコ
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
a future-flavored, mysterious chocolate.
温めて混ぜたら絶対
If we warm it up and mix it, absolutely,
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
someday it will become the most happily delicious flavor!
いっせーのーで サンキューソーマッチ ヒューマンズタイム
Ready, set, go! Thank you so much, human's time!
ねぇ ひとつだけ聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask you just one thing?
私のこと...
About how I feel...
私のこと
About me...
会えるかも今日は
Maybe I'll get to see you today,
心が騒いで
my heart is all stirred up,
スキップしたくなった
making me want to skip along,
ときめきに踊る瞬間
in this moment dancing with excitement.
私のことなど
You probably don't care about someone like me at all,
たぶん気にしてないのだけど
but...
ここにいるんだよ
I am right here,
私はここよ
I am right here!
自信が揺れ動き
My confidence wavers—
嫌われてないかな？
is it possible you hate me?
勢いでとにかく
Driven by impulse,
挨拶だ！
I'll just greet you anyway!
やっと晴れたね
It's finally cleared up,
ぱーっと晴れたね
it's completely cleared up,
そして元気なるね
and it makes me feel so energetic!
おはようの代わりに背中を叩いて
Instead of a "good morning," I'll pat you on the back and say,
「さあ、行くよ！」
"Now, let's go!"
やっと晴れたら
When it finally clears up,
ぱーっと晴れたら
when it completely clears up,
きっと元気な笑顔
I'm sure to wear a cheerful smile,
なんだか今のこの気持ちが切なくなったよ！
though somehow, this current feeling of mine turned a little bittersweet!
授業も上の空
Even during class my mind is absent,
遠くを眺めた
gazing far away.
君が言う「トモダチの半分」
When you say 'half of a friend'...
夢見るだけ許して
Just let me dream.
触わって閉じ込めなきゃだから
Because if I don't hold it and lock it away...
動き出そうよ
Let's start moving forward.
自分らしくね
In my own way.
楽しく生きるの
Living life happily,
毎日が奇跡
every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより
Rather than regretting staying silent,
勇気出そう！
I'll muster up my courage!
ずっと前から ほんと前から
For a long time, truly for a long time,
聴いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you.
私から最初に
From me first,
伝えてしまえ 大好きです！
I'll just say it: I love you!
ずっと前だよ ほんと前だよ
'It was a long time ago, truly a long time ago.'
聞いたことに答えて
Answer what I asked.
どんな風に感じてるの？
How do you feel about it?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything!
楽しく生きるの
Living life happily,
毎日が奇跡
every day is a miracle.
本当は不安... でも
To be honest, I'm anxious... but
勇気出そう！
I'll muster up my courage!
行くよ？ / うん！
Here we go! / Yeah!
ずっと前から ほんと前から
For a long time, truly for a long time,
聴いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you.
私から最初に
From me first,
伝えてしまえ 大好きです！
I'll just say it: I love you!
ずっと前だよ ほんと前だよ
'It was a long time ago, truly a long time ago.'
聞いたことに答えて
Answer what I asked.
どんな風に感じてるの？
How do you feel about it?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything!
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を射す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you,
ねえ 教えて
hey, tell me.
教えて
Tell me.
世界は恋に落ちている
[Title: The World is Falling in Love]
すれ違う言葉に ちょっとだけの後悔
A little regret over our crossed words,
涙こぼれて
tears spill over.
忙しい感情 鼓動にリンクする
Busy emotions link to my heartbeat.
チューニング 確かめたいんだ
I want to confirm our tuning.
目的ばっかに囚われて
Trapped only by my goals,
大事なものがくすんで逃げて
important things get blurred and slip away.
今日もリスタート
Restarting today as well.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を射す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything,
ねえ 聞かせて
hey, let me hear.
聞かせて
Let me hear.
ただ1ミリが遠くて
Just one millimeter feels so far away,
駆け抜けた日々
through the days we ran through,
に
in those days,
忘れない 忘れられない 輝く1ページ
unforgettable, impossible to forget, a shining page.
お似合いの二人になんだか複雑な
Looking at the suitable pair, I feel a complex...
気持ちがいるよ
feeling inside me,
初めての感情 鼓動にリンクする
my first time feeling this, linking to my heartbeat.
体温計 壊れちゃったかな？
Did the thermometer break?
壊れちゃったかな...
I wonder if it broke...
自分のこと分からないまま
Still not understanding myself,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even went and gave advice to her...
胸が痛いや...
My chest hurts so much...
世界は恋に落ちている
The whole world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を刺す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
気づいたこの想いは
These feelings I've realized...
「もう、遅いの」
"It's already too late."
あの子の方がかわいいの
That girl is cuter than me,
知ってるよだけど
I know that, but...
バカ...
Dummy...
君のこと全部分かりたいって思っちゃう
I find myself wanting to understand everything about you.
色が恋だって初めて気づいたの
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to turn my way.
遅かったけど諦めたくない
I was late, but I don't want to give up.
だって 好きだから
Because... I love you.
春に咲いた花が恋をした
The flower that bloomed in spring fell in love.
花は必死に上を向いて笑った
The flower desperately looked up and smiled.
青い夏の蕾も恋をした
The bud of blue summer also fell in love.
咲かない花と火薬の匂い
An unblooming flower and the scent of gunpowder.
ホントの気持ち言葉にして
If I turn my true feelings into words,
大事なこと話せたら
and can talk about what's important,
今日もリスタート
I'll restart again today.
鈍感な君だから
Since you're so dense,
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you right now.
「ねえ、好きです」
"Hey, I love you."
世界は恋に落ちている
The whole world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を刺す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
「ねえ、聞かせて」
"Hey, let me know."
たぐり寄せてもうゼロセンチ
Pulling you close, now at zero centimeters.
駆け抜けた日々に
Through the days we ran through,
忘れない 忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget,
輝く1ページ
this shining page.
はい！ということで！
Alright, and with that!
ここまでは
Up until now,
アキさま、ロボ子、ござるに、ふーちゃんと
Aki-sama, Roboco, Gozaru, and Fuu-chan...
一緒に歌わせていただきました！
joined me to sing!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
さてさて、ここからは...
Now then, from here on...
なんと！重大告知が2つあります！
We have two big announcements!
まず1つ目が...
First up...
こちら！ドドン！
This! Ta-da!
癒月ちょこ 誕生記念2026グッズ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 Merch!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います！
Let me introduce them in more detail!
まずは、こちら！
First, this one!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's Cushion!
いや、これね...
So, you see...
ちょこの誕生日といえば...
When it comes to Choco's birthday...
毎年Nardack先生、ありがとうございますということで！
A huge thanks to Nardack-sensei, as always!
今年もNardack先生に
This year again, Nardack-sensei...
めちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
drew a super wonderful illustration for us!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで...
The theme this time is Valentine's Day...
ちょっとね、チョコレートを抱きながら...
so holding chocolate...
ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
we made it into a chocolate-bar style cushion this time!
可愛いでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので...
The size is just right, like a pillow...
ちょっとね、お昼寝の時とか仮眠用に
so for power naps or afternoon rest,
すやーってできる感じで使ってもらえます！
you can use it to peacefully sleep on!
そして続いては、こちら！
And moving on to the next one, here it is!
なんと！
Believe it or not!
今回初めてちょっとね
For the very first time,
お菓子が作れる
we have something to make sweets!
なんとなんと
Believe it or not,
ちょこのチョコレート型ー！
Choco's chocolate mold!
耐熱も 冷却も
It works for heat-resistant baking and freezing,
あったかいのも 冷たいのも 両方使えちゃって
so you can use it for both hot and cold items!
ちょっとね チョコレート… チョコメイドな今回は
This time, as Choco, chocolate-themed...
チョコレート型になっておりますー！
it's in the shape of a chocolate mold!
ま、マフィンとかね クッキーとか
Like for muffins, cookies,
あとはまあ普通に 冷やしかためて チョコレート入れたりとか
or just chilling and hardening melted chocolate in it,
なんか色々使えるから ぜひみんなも作ってみてねー！
it can be used for so many things, so give it a try!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
お待たせいたしましたー！
Thank you for waiting!
ちょこのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Choco's Sleepy Plushie Keyholder!
ま、ちょこと言えばね 睡眠ということで
Well, speaking of Choco, sleep comes to mind,
超ロングスリーパーのちょこが
so Choco, the super long sleeper,
今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって
this time has become a plushie keyholder!
ちょっとすやすやぬいぐるみで 作らせていただきましたー！
I had this cute sleepy plushie made!
ま、ずっとね 肌身離さず持っていれば いつか…聴こえてくるかもしれない！
If you keep it with you at all times, maybe someday... you might hear something!
そして 今年もございます！
And we have it again this year!
癒月ちょこ書き下ろし台本の 耳舐めASMR台本ー！
Licking ASMR voice drama written by Yuzuki Choco!
撮りましたよ ちょこのASMRボイス！
I recorded them—Choco's ASMR voice packs!
今回ね 耳舐めの方は3つございます！
This time, there are three ear-licking voice packs!
1つ目が『溶けかけのチョコレート』ー！
The first one is "Melting Chocolate"!
いや こちらはね あ、ちょっと…
Well, this one is... a bit...
あの 皆さまがご想像しているより
a bit more than you might imagine...
ちょっとあの…あの… エッチちかもしれないんですけどー
a bit... spicy, perhaps!
配信ではね 絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので
It's a voice set you definitely can't do on a stream,
ぜひともね 皆さま ご購入して聴いてみてください！
so please buy it and give it a listen!
そして もう1つが 『残業あとのご褒美デザート』ということで
And another one is "Reward Dessert After Overtime"!
こちらはね ちょとの同棲シチュエーションとなっております！
This one is a living-together scenario with Choco!
はい ちょこが残業してきて 帰ってきたときの…
Yes, when Choco comes home after working overtime...
うーん… ま、デザートはちょこなのかな？ 君なのかな？ どっちなんだろうねー？
Hmm, is the dessert Choco, or is it you? Which could it be?
ま、ちょっと聴いてみてよー！
Well, give it a listen!
そしてそして！ 『年下幼馴染のツンデレバレンタイン』ということで
And next! "Younger Childhood Friend's Tsundere Valentine"!
今回はね 聴いている君たちが ちょっと隣の家のお兄ちゃんになった気分で 聴いてみてください！
This time, try listening to it as if you're the older guy next door!
こちらもね 耳舐めボイスとなっておりますが
This one is also an ear-licking voice,
なんとこちら ドMの方は絶対に聴いていただけたら ちょっとニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います！
and if you're a big masochist, I think listening to this will definitely make you grin!
はい！ そしてそして フルセットをご購入の方！
Yes! And for those who purchase the full set!
フルセット特典！
The full set bonus!
今回はなんと初めて！ チェキ風ブロマイドカードになりましたー！
For the first time ever, it's a cheki-style bromide card!
ちょっとこちらね 数量限定で 直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージが入っておりますー！
For the limited-quantity version, it includes a handwritten signature and foil-stamped message!
カキカキしちゃうよー！
I'll be signing them!
通常バージョンは 箔押し複製サインと 複製メッセージが入ります！
The regular version comes with a foil-stamped print signature and message!
そしてね 特典がもう1つ！
And there's another bonus!
フルセット購入特典として 『ヤキモチのギュー』ASMRボイスが入っております！
As a full set bonus, the "Jealous Hugs" ASMR voice pack is included!
いや こちらはね ちょっとあの 甘々の甘のボイスなので
Well, this one is super, super sweet,
ま、ちょっとね 普段はちょこ嫉妬しないんですけど 何に嫉妬してるかは聴いてからのお楽しみなんですけど
so normally Choco doesn't get jealous, but what I'm jealous of is something to look forward to!
ちょっとぜひぜひ ニヤニヤしながら聴いといてください！
So please enjoy listening to it with a grin on your face!
ぜひ手に入れてください！
Please be sure to get it!
そしてそして！
And next!
重大告知！ 2つ目は…こちらー！
A major announcement! The second one is... this!
…ねぇ ちょこたち もう二度と会えないの？
"Hey... Choco and the others, will we never meet again?"
不思議ね。 キミの言葉を聞くと なんだか元気が出てきちゃう。
"It's strange. Hearing your words somehow gives me energy."
ちょこ もしや…問よ。
"Choco, could it be... a question?"
ちょこのことをもっともっと 大好きになってほしい。
"I want you to love Choco more and more."
ねぇ もしよければキミに… ちょこの思い出話 聴いてほしいの。
"Hey, if it's okay with you, I'd like you to listen to Choco's memories."
[「The Beginning」 12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース＆連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート]
["The Beginning" 12 Consecutive Months Original Song Release & Voice Drama Project Start]
[3/15から毎月15日0時 オリジナル楽曲リリース]
[Original song releases on the 15th of every month at midnight starting 3/15]
[豪華アーティスト参加]
[Featuring gorgeous artists]
[癒月ちょことあなたのストーリーを辿った全12話のボイスドラマ]
[12-episode voice drama following the story of Yuzuki Choco and you]
[「The Beginning」 project 始動！]
["The Beginning" project launch!]
はーい！ というわけで 癒月ちょこ
Alright! So, Yuzuki Choco's...
12ヶ月連続オリ曲リリースが決定し…
12 consecutive months of original song releases has been decided!
しかもこちら
And what's more...
なんとオリ曲にストーリー連動のボイスドラマが
surprisingly, a story-linked voice drama for these original songs...
一緒にリリースされます！
will be released together!
こちらね、約1話から12話まで
Here, from episodes 1 to 12,
1曲ずつに連動して
linked to each individual song,
ボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててくだーさい！
there will also be a voice drama, so please look forward to it!
そして今回はね、その記念すべき...
And this time...
1曲目を、これから披露したいと思います！
I'd like to perform the memorable first song!
それでは聞いてください、「キミの秒針」
Now then, please listen to "Kimi no Byoushin".
戻れないから
Because I can't go back,
また 愛おしさが増す
my affection grows even deeper.
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
君から受け取った 壊れそうなストーリー
The fragile story I received from you,
どこまでも広がる 青い空
the blue sky spreading endlessly.
変わらない毎日も 色のナイ夢も
Even the unchanging days and color-less dreams,
手放して始めよう
let's let them go and start anew.
不安の夜を数え
Counting the anxious nights,
泣きながら迎えた
welcoming them with tears...
朝でもいい
Even a morning like that is fine.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I spread out the carved memories.
戻れないから また
Because I can't go back, again
愛おしさが増す
my affection grows.
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
二人で温めた 大切なストーリー
The precious story we warmed together,
遠くまで続いた 果てない道
the endless road continuing into the distance.
疲れたら代わるから そう言ってくれた
"If you get tired, I'll take over," you told me.
優しさに触れて癒えた
Healed by touching your kindness,
受け入れてくれたこと
that you accepted me,
忘れない 嬉しくて泣いた日
I won't forget the day I cried out of happiness.
雨上がりの胸に
In my chest after the rain,
架かった虹のように綺麗だ
it's beautiful like a rainbow hanging in the sky.
君からの言葉
The words from you,
一つ一つが 今も宝物
each and every one is still a treasure.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me,
輝ける この気持ち
this feeling can shine,
届けよう
I'll deliver it to you.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I spread out the carved memories.
戻れないから また
Because I can't go back, again
愛おしさが増す 君に会いたいよ
my affection grows, I want to see you.
雨上がりの胸に
In my chest after the rain,
架かった虹のように綺麗だ
it's beautiful like a rainbow hanging in the sky.
君からの言葉
The words from you,
一つ一つが 今も宝物
each and every one is still a treasure.
はい！ということで、みんなどうだったかなー？
All right! So, how was it everyone?
今回の新曲「キミの秒針」は、シドのマオ様が作詞
My new song this time, "Kimi no Byoushin," has lyrics by SID's Mao-sama,
そして恵風安様が作曲、編曲、
composed and arranged by Atsushi Mimori-sama,
そして編曲にはなんと、加藤貴之様も加わっていただきました！
and for the arrangement, Takayuki Kato-sama also joined in!
今回はー、ボイスドラマ連動企画の第1弾としてー、
This time, as the first part of the voice drama collaboration project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような楽曲に仕上がっておりますー！
it was finished as a song serving as the overall theme song for the story!
ま、ドラマの鍵となるね、秒針というメタファーにも要注目してください！
Also, please pay close attention to the metaphor of the "second hand" which is key to the drama!
はい！
Yes!
マオさんだけではなく、このあとね、豪華アーティストの皆様にもたーくさん書いていただいたので！
Not just Mao-san, but many wonderful artists wrote songs after this too!
皆様、リリースお楽しみにー！
Everyone, look forward to the releases!
こちらの「キミの秒針」は、各音楽サイト…
This "Kimi no Byoushin" will be on various music sites...
ちょっと間が開いちゃうんだけど、3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
There's a bit of a gap, but it's scheduled to stream starting at midnight on March 15th!
ま、ちょっとね、公開まで時間が開くから、それまでこの配信何度も見返してみてください！
Since there's some time before it's released, please rewatch this stream many times until then!
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it a lot, okay?
そしてそしてー！
And, and...!
MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしててくださーい！
The MV will also be released at a later date, so please look forward to it!
はい！
Yes!
ということで、今日のちょこの生誕ライブはどうだったかなー？
So then, how was Choco's birthday live today?
ま、この後はー、すぐにー、
Well, coming up right after this...
ちょっとね、冒頭、最初の方でお披露目したー、
as teased at the very beginning,
ノエルちゃんとラミたんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があってー、
there'll be the MV release of "Hatsukoi Daisensou" with Noel-chan, Lamy-tan, and me!
そのあと！
And after that!
メン限でちょっと、ライブとー、撮影会の続きとかー、
for members only, we'll continue with the live show, photo session, and...
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
doing some situation dramas that you can only see in members-only mode!
ぜひぜひ！気になる人は見に来てくださいー！
So if you're interested, please come watch!
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, see you all again later!
おつかれーとー！
Otsukareito~!
ん～…ちゅっ！
Mmm... *kiss*!